<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Zealand on Tenkr Scholarship</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/categories/new-zealand/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New Zealand on Tenkr Scholarship</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/categories/new-zealand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand | 164 Scholarships</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand--164-scholarships/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand--164-scholarships/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand | 164 Scholarships
by Scholarships Corner | Jun 27, 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;University of Otago Scholarships, new zealand scholarships
University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand is a marvelous opportunity for all domestic and international students. Do you want to pursue your post-graduate degree in New Zealand on scholarship? Take the chance; your luck has taken you to the right page. The University of Otago Doctoral Scholarship supports funding for doctoral students to research relevant areas of expertise. Candidates applying for the Otago scholarships must be seeking to attain the first doctoral qualification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These scholarships in New Zealand will refine your research skills according to the current market trends. These research scholarships will combine classroom lectures, tutorials, lab experimentation, assignments, and reading materials. The University of Otago, New Zealand’s first university, started with few resources and has now extended its sphere from Invercargill to Auckland. This international University has a history of passing out around 4500 post-graduates and more than 1500 doctoral students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With 13 flagship research centers, the University of Otago has gained research and teaching excellence by winning three Prime Minister’s Science Prizes in the last decade. New Zealand’s top university has spent $208 million in external research funding. The Otago has topped the TEC’s Educational performance indicators that express the performance and retention rating of the students. Moreover, the University has won the Supreme Award six times over the past nine years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The international scholarship opportunities by the University of Otago will prove to be a worthy option for the participants. The Otago students are recognized for their negotiating, interpersonal, conceptual, independent judgment, and analytical skills. Therefore, global employers used to love Otago students. More than 90% of Otago students get jobs quickly once they complete their education. You will get the opportunity to learn from world-class lecturers and professors who stand shoulder-to-shoulder with the best globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34;&gt;University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand: &lt;a href=&#34;#university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Zealand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University of Otago&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;number-of-scholarships&#34;&gt;Number of Scholarships: &lt;a href=&#34;#number-of-scholarships&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;180 University of Otago postgraduate research scholarships in New Zealand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;degree-level&#34;&gt;Degree Level: &lt;a href=&#34;#degree-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional Doctorates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scholarship-duration&#34;&gt;Scholarship Duration: &lt;a href=&#34;#scholarship-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The duration of the research scholarship is 36 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-university-of-otago-scholarship-benefits-2024&#34;&gt;The University of Otago Scholarship Benefits 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#the-university-of-otago-scholarship-benefits-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support funding for doctoral research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NZ $32,544 stipend annually for Doctors of Philosophy and other professional doctorates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domestic tuition fee waiver for Doctors of Philosophy for up to 36 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition fee waiver for up to 36 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to conducting research in an International environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of advanced research methods and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-of-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria of the University of Otago Scholarships 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-of-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All domestic and international students can apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completion of Master’s degree with at least 0.75 EFTS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant advanced papers should be followed with the degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case a Master’s degree is not completed, the grades of all relevant advanced-level papers will be considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If prior qualifications are completed by any other University, the GPA score should be mentioned on the transcripts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s potential for research is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s track record of research is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommendation of the concerned Head of the department is necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34;&gt;How to Apply for the University of Otago Scholarships 2024? &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students have to apply through the University’s website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete the application for admission with the relevant qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer all questions carefully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review your application form carefully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After the submission of the application, an invitation to apply for the scholarship will be received in your e-Vision portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;selection-criteria-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34;&gt;Selection Criteria for the University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand: &lt;a href=&#34;#selection-criteria-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research potential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic merit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;application-deadline&#34;&gt;Application Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#application-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no closing date. The applicant may apply anytime throughout the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.otago.ac.nz/study/scholarships/database/search/otago014687.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
