<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on KnightMoves</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on KnightMoves</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:59:05 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MandelaWashingtonFellowship2025USA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/mandelawashingtonfellowship2025usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/mandelawashingtonfellowship2025usa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2025, The Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 in USA will bring up to 700 young leaders to the United States for an extensive executive-style program aimed at developing skills and enabling Fellows to take on leadership roles in their communities and industries. Selected fellows will participate in a six-week Leadership Institute at a U.S. college or university where they will share their experiences with U.S citizens and other African Fellows and learn from them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this fully-funded fellowship, Fellows will have the opportunity to explore various industries other than their daily work which will help to expand their expertise and strengthen their skills. Other than this, fellows will be able to meet with U.S. Government Officials and renowned business leaders. This US exchange program will enhance your work with the help of new connections, skills, and ideas. After the event will end, fellows can join the global Alumni Network that will be useful for them to look for creative solutions to most common problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will have a life-changing experience from this leadership program. Through this fellowship for Africans, participants will establish powerful networks with both Africans and Americans. You’ll be able to regain your self-confidence and motivation to give back to your community. Students will be studying Business, Civic Engagement, or Public Management hosted by U.S. colleges or universities which will add to their existing knowledge and teach them new concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mandela Washington Fellowship does not discriminate against applicants on the basis of any protected characteristic as defined by U.S. law, including race, ethnicity, colour, national origin, sex, age, religion, geographic location, education, income, socioeconomic status, ability, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, or any other. The Fellowship is dedicated to accessibility, fairness, equity, and inclusion. If you belong to one of the countries mentioned above, feel free to apply for this international fellowship program in U.S before the deadline approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-organization&#34;&gt;Host Organization &lt;a href=&#34;#host-organization&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Young African Leaders Initiative (YALI) Network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mandela-fellowship-location&#34;&gt;Mandela Fellowship Location: &lt;a href=&#34;#mandela-fellowship-location&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington DC, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fellowship-duration&#34;&gt;Fellowship Duration &lt;a href=&#34;#fellowship-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 weeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34;&gt;Benefits of Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 in the USA: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;J-1 visa support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Round-trip travel from the Fellow’s home city to the United States and necessary domestic U.S. travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Departure from an eligible Fellowship country in Africa to the United States&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Six-week Leadership Institute
Concluding Summit in Washington, D.C.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limited accident and sickness benefit plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Housing and meals during the program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optional four-week Professional Development Experience for up to 100 Fellows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fellows will participate in a six-week Leadership Institute at a U.S. college or university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to interact with other fellows attending the event.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fellows will become a part of Global Alumni Network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be no discrimination on the basis of race, gender, color or any other protected characteristic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants will get a chance to meet U.S officials and business executives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a wonderful chance to explore USA without financial burden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria for Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 in the USA: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be young African leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are between the ages of 25 and 35 years old till September 10, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not have to be either U.S. citizens or permanent residents of U.S.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be eligible to receive a United States J-1 visa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must not be employees or family members including spouses, parents, children, or siblings of any employees of the U.S. Government Departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be proficient in reading, writing, and speaking English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be citizens and permanent residents of one of the following countries:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Angola, Benin, Botswana, Burkina Faso, Burundi, Cameroon, Cabo Verde, Central African Republic, Chad, Comoros, Republic of the Congo, Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC), Cote d’Ivoire, Djibouti, Equatorial Guinea, Eritrea, Eswatini, Ethiopia, Gabon, The Gambia, Ghana, Guinea, Guinea-Bissau, Kenya, Lesotho, Liberia, Madagascar, Malawi, Mali, Mauritania, Mauritius, Mozambique, Namibia, Niger, Nigeria, Rwanda, Sao Tome and Principe, Senegal, Seychelles, Sierra Leone, Somalia, South Africa, South Sudan, Sudan, Tanzania, Togo, Uganda, Zambia, or Zimbabwe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not have to be Alumni or former participant of the Mandela Washington Fellowship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025&#34;&gt;How to apply for Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin with new User registration on the link given to apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agree to the terms and conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create your account by entering your email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A confirmation email will be sent on your email address to create a new account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This link will automatically expire after 60 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create your account by entering a password of your email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide the general information asked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide your CV details in the sections already given.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mention your education and professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List your professional skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enter your demographic details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mention any previous U.S experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer short essay questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete the application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click the blue button “Review and Submit”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your application will be submitted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selected candidates will then further have interviews.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-mandela-fellowship-2025&#34;&gt;Documents required for Mandela Fellowship 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-mandela-fellowship-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional trainings and certifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community and Volunteer work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awards, honors, grants and scholarships received.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associations and affiliations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English language proficiency test scores.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International passport.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2025-mandela-fellowship-deadline&#34;&gt;2025 Mandela Fellowship Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#2025-mandela-fellowship-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The last date to apply is 10th September, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mandelawashingtonfellowship.org/apply/&#34;&gt;Apply Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIST Scholarship in South Korea 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/gist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/gist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://scholarshipscorner.website/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/GIST-Scholarships-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;GIST Korea&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology in South Korea welcomes skilled and talented students, researchers, and technical individuals to pursue their MS, PhD, and MS leading to PhD under the GIST Scholarship 2024. The GIST scholarship for international students in Korea provides them with a bright chance to create a strong research base for further development of science and technology. Moreover, the best scholarship in South Korea’s top universities provides opportunities for students to work and promote collaborative foreign and domestic research programs in the industrial sector as well as in academia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GIST scholars are equipped with world-class knowledge and skills regarding science and technology through research-oriented projects and courses. Furthermore, GIST’s fully-funded scholarship is a project of the university with the South Korean Ministry of Science and Technology. The ministry provides full financial support to the students of GIST in order to promote scientific technologists and encourage them toward more innovations. For this, the university offers students multiple fields of study related to science, technology, and research. The GIST university courses include Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Material Science and Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Earth Science and Environmental Engineering, Life Science, Physics and Photon Science, Chemistry and Biomedical Science, Nanobio Materials and Electronics, Integrated Technology, and Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GIST was established by Korean Government in 1993 and since then the institute has been home to world-class researchers and sciencetists. Moreover, the top-notch lecturers of Korean institutes come from GIST. GIST has proved itself as the first national university in Korea which has adopted an innovative educational system based on a comprehensive and foundational science curriculum. Moreover, GIST is the first Korean university that has made a thesis quality certification mandatory thing. That is why the institute is ranked 1st in the number of citations of professors in South Korea for 14 consecutive years and also the GIST is ranked 4th in QS World University Ranking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GIST Scholarships for MS and PhD students is a milestone towards achieving the goal of the institute i.e. A proud creator of future science and technology. In order to lead in the world, all classes are taught in English, and the thesis is also written in the English language. GIST understands the importance of learning and utilizing an international language for better collaboration and development. The scholars of the GIST international scholarship in South Korea will learn the Korean culture while staying for a maximum of three, seven, or eight years for MS, PhD, or Integrated MS/PhD programs respectively. The following comprehensively explains the financial benefits along with the eligibility criteria and an understandable procedure to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gist-scholarship-in-south-korea-2024&#34;&gt;GIST Scholarship in South Korea 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#gist-scholarship-in-south-korea-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South Korea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology (GIST)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;degree-level&#34;&gt;Degree Level: &lt;a href=&#34;#degree-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrated MS and PhD Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-gist-scholarship-in-south-korea&#34;&gt;Benefits of the GIST Scholarship in South Korea: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-the-gist-scholarship-in-south-korea&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All international students will be getting 100% support in the tuition fee i.e. the tuition fee will be waived.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS students will be given a monthly stipend of 140,000 Won.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD students will be given a monthly stipend of 295,000 Won.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both MS and PhD students will be given a meal allowance of 100,000 Won. (Note: Students have to complete at least 9 credits in the previous semester in order to get student and meal allowance).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An international student allowance of 120,000 Won will be given to both MS and PhD students, however, the student has to maintain a 3 or higher GPA out of 4.5 in the previous semester.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All MS students participating in research projects will get a research assistantship of 5,461,249  won per year while PhD students participating in research projects will get a research assistantship of 12,513,688 won per year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A one-way flight to Korea will be reimbursed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;60% of national health insurance will be covered. Health insurance also includes annual medical checkups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-of-the-gist-scholarship-2024-in-south-korea&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria of the GIST Scholarship 2024 in South Korea: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-of-the-gist-scholarship-2024-in-south-korea&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must or expect to hold a final degree before enrollment at GIST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s bachelor’s degree must be equivalent to a Korean bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be an international student.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be proficient in the English language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-gist-scholarship-2024&#34;&gt;How to apply for the GIST Scholarship 2024? &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-gist-scholarship-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to apply online for the GIST South Korea scholarship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to submit a matriculation fee, however, the matriculation fee can be waived on the recommendation of the dean/head of the department/college.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In order to apply successfully, all the applicants must carefully fill out the GIST online application form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t leave blanks instead write NA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-the-gist-scholarships-2023&#34;&gt;Documents Required for the GIST Scholarships 2023: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-the-gist-scholarships-2023&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official degrees and transcripts are required. Apostille is preferred or even notarized copies are acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two letters of recommendation must have the signatures and stamps of the recommenders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The recommenders do not have to send the letters independently or separately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official English language test report i.e. TOEFL (BT) 80 / TOEFL (PBT) 550 / IELTS 6.5 / TOEIC 750 / NEW TEPS 327 is the requirement. In case you do not get your test result in time. Your home university can give you a professional English language proficiency certificate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A copy of the applicant’s passport is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gist-scholarship-application-deadline&#34;&gt;GIST Scholarship Application Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#gist-scholarship-application-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application deadline for the Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology scholarship in South Korea 2024 is October 14, 2023.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gist.ac.kr/iadm/html/sub05/0502.html?mode=V&amp;amp;no=205383&amp;amp;GotoPage=1&#34;&gt;Official Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
