<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tenkr Scholarship</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tenkr Scholarship</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chevening Scholarship 2025 in UK | Fully Funded | Study in UK by Scholarships Corner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/chevening-scholarship-2025-in-uk--fully-funded--study-in-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/chevening-scholarship-2025-in-uk--fully-funded--study-in-uk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;chevening scholarship, uk scholarships, europe scholarships
Chevening Scholarship is one of the top scholarships in the UK and it provides a fully-funded scholarship for a one-year master’s program in the UK universities to all aspiring candidates from a Chevening member or eligible countries. As the UK is home to the world’s best educational institutions, it has always been a study destination for students across the world. Chevening Uk Government Scholarship program is a golden opportunity for talented, self-motivated, and skilled students to excel in their careers and achieve their goals while studying and getting trained from world-class educational institutes in which they were not able to study otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The United Kingdom is the most diverse country due to its ability to inhibit different cultures, ethnicities, and nations. Therefore, Chevening is the best master’s scholarship UK for those students who have a great tilt towards learning about different cultures and who are resilient and welcoming towards other nationalities and ethnicities. Furthermore, the UK offers a one-year master’s program which is rare in other countries and goal-oriented individuals know the real meaning and importance of timing to start a career, therefore, the master’s in the UK is always preferred and Chevening is a platform from where the dream to study in the UK’s top universities comes true. Besides all these Chevening Scholarships in Europe provide extraordinary opportunities to study in the UK and also provide a chance to master English language skills which is an international language and a stepping stone towards development and growth in the international area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Chevening scholars are proven to be the change-makers of this global community. The Cheveners are coping with the global and local challenges through their creative minds and a network of their own Chevening community. Their actual journey starts after the completion of their master’s under the Chevening Scholarship UK in which they commit to serving their communities while returning back to their home countries for at least two years since its inception in 1983, The competitive scholarship program in the UK – the Chevening fully-funded scholarship for international students – has been proving itself as a milestone towards elevating the careers, transforming the communities, shifting and building the perspectives, and building international bridges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chevening scholars have set examples in almost every field of life while serving humanity. For example, the Chevening scholars dedicated 6,467 hours of their time to community services while studying their master’s courses in the UK and they have broken volunteering records. Similarly, Amina Mehmood, a Chevening Alumna joined the forces of the UK Foreign Secretary to lead Girl’s Education Initiative. There are numerous examples that encourage graduates to be a part of top-class scholarships in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chevening gathers scholars and potential leaders from over 160 countries and territories which creates networks and builds friendships, and memories. This environment prevails the co-existence among the nations and reduces the resistive nature and extremism. Moreover, Chevening possesses more than 50,000 strong alumni which include 18 current or former heads of the state or government. Chevening Awards also create alumni who excel in other fields of life besides politics. As the Chevening scholarships for international students are highly competitive, their process and eligibility also require keen interest and accuracy. In order to get selected for this fully-funded UK scholarship program, one must fulfill the given requirement. make sure to read the guidelines on how to prepare for the Chevening Scholarship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;chevening-scholarship-2025-in-the-uk&#34;&gt;Chevening Scholarship 2025 in the UK: &lt;a href=&#34;#chevening-scholarship-2025-in-the-uk&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;United Kingdom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-organization&#34;&gt;Host Organization: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-organization&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chevening Awards are awarded by the Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO) and partner organizations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;course-level&#34;&gt;Course Level: &lt;a href=&#34;#course-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s Degree Program (Masters/MPhil)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;course-duration&#34;&gt;Course Duration: &lt;a href=&#34;#course-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 year Master’s Degree Scholarship Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-chevening-scholarship-2025&#34;&gt;Benefits of the Chevening Scholarship 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-the-chevening-scholarship-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chevening will pay the quarantine cost if booked by Diversity Travel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The tuition fee will be covered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chevening scholars are not required to pay any visa fee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A monthly living allowance will be paid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An economy class return air ticket will be given.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;UK additional grants will be given to cover extra expenditures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the TB test is applicable in any of the Chevener’s countries, the amount for the test will be reimbursed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Chevening scholars will receive cash cards which will be given on the day of arrival.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chevening-scholarship-requirements-2025&#34;&gt;Chevening Scholarship Requirements 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#chevening-scholarship-requirements-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be a citizen of Chevening eligible country or territory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be able to return to his/her own country for at least two years after the completion of the award.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be applied for a full-time master’s degree program, not less or more than 12 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must have attended an undergraduate degree equivalent to an upper second class 2:1 honors degree in the UK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has applied to three different university courses and has received an unconditional letter for one of the courses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must have two years of work experience or work experience of 2800 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicants who are of British nationality or dual British citizens are not eligible to apply unless the applicants are citizens of British overseas territory and are applying from Hong Kong.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicants who hold refugee status in a non-Chevening country are not eligible. Only those refugee status applicants eligible who are in Chevening member countries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicants who are employees, former employees, or relatives of current and former employees of her Majesty’s Government, or a staff member of the Association member of Commonwealth Universities can not apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants who are employees, former employees, or relatives of an employee of a Chevening partner organization can apply but they can not receive a Chevening partner award from that particular organization in which they or their relatives work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant who is already in the UK under the UK’s Government funding can not apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-chevening-scholarship-2025&#34;&gt;How to Apply for the Chevening Scholarship 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-chevening-scholarship-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to apply online through the online application system (OAS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicants are recommended to apply through Google Chrome while using a laptop or a PC rather than a mobile or tablet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must have applied for three different courses in the UK’s universities because for the Chevening scholarship in the United Kingdom, an unconditional offer letter for any one course is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In order to apply successfully the size and format of the files just need the requirements that the documents must be in JPG, PNG, or PDF form and not larger than 5MB.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The length of the file names must not exceed 50 characters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read step by step guide how to apply for th Chevening Scholarship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chevening-scholarship-application-process-2025&#34;&gt;Chevening Scholarship Application Process 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#chevening-scholarship-application-process-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application must be submitted in English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must remember the username and password in order to be able to log back into OAS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In your application, provide accurate information, especially your contact and e-mail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid using the browser’s back and ‘forward buttons, this may lead you out of the application system. Instead, use the menu from the application form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application includes four essay questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The essay must not be less than 100 words and the maximum essay word count is 500 words. Ensure that you meet this requirement to answer all questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application has no autosave button, so you must save the application on your own. Remember each online application session expires every 60 minutes. Try to save your application before the expiry of time otherwise the unsaved entries will be lost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An application is a lengthy process, you can log out from the application and can start any other time while using the username and password and the given link via e-mail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have only three chances to submit the eligibility form correctly. In case of failure, your application will not be submitted and you can submit your application for next year only.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you have clicked the submit button you can not modify your application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have only one chance per year to submit your application and only one application is accepted. That is why your first submitted application will be considered final.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your application must contain two reference letters. Make sure your referees are able to be contacted if needed. The British High Commission contacts and verifies the authenticity of the reference letters from your referees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tips-for-chevening-scholarship-reference-letters&#34;&gt;Tips for Chevening Scholarship Reference Letters: &lt;a href=&#34;#tips-for-chevening-scholarship-reference-letters&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reference letters must answer the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The referee’s contact details: address, e-mail, and phone number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For how long the referee has known the applicant?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In what capacity does the referee know the applicant?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When did the referee have the last contact with the applicant?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A brief endorsement that explains the applicant’s skills and ability to be part of the Chevening Scholarship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tips-for-a-successful-chevening-scholarship-application-form&#34;&gt;Tips for a Successful Chevening Scholarship Application Form: &lt;a href=&#34;#tips-for-a-successful-chevening-scholarship-application-form&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must correctly answer all the pre-screen in order to access the application form. A lot of candidates are rejected in this very initial stage because of incorrect answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once the applicant has access to the application all the eligibility parts must be attended to carefully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must not overlook the work experience section. Make sure to enter the correct number of work hours and the correct number of working weeks. The applicant must not be unrealistic while entering the work hours (e.g. 30,000 instead of 20 hours/week).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicants who indicate dual citizenship are rejected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure you do not enter one experience twice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is recommended that you have the same courses selected at three different universities which shows your commitment to your goals (the name may differ).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not choose duplicate courses for the same university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carefully fill out your declaration part in which you have to answer according to Yes or NO.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not copy and paste your answers from other websites it will show plagiarism and your application will be rejected. Answer with originality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not repeat the same answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure to fulfill the word count requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is recommended to have an English Proficiency Certificate even if the Chevening Scholarship does not require any proof but it can be the requirement of the university in which you are applying of the university you are applying and you are expected an unconditional offer letter from that university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;chevening-scholarship-application-deadline&#34;&gt;Chevening Scholarship Application Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#chevening-scholarship-application-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application deadline for the scholarship is November 5, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chevening.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand | 164 Scholarships</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand--164-scholarships/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand--164-scholarships/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand | 164 Scholarships
by Scholarships Corner | Jun 27, 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;University of Otago Scholarships, new zealand scholarships
University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand is a marvelous opportunity for all domestic and international students. Do you want to pursue your post-graduate degree in New Zealand on scholarship? Take the chance; your luck has taken you to the right page. The University of Otago Doctoral Scholarship supports funding for doctoral students to research relevant areas of expertise. Candidates applying for the Otago scholarships must be seeking to attain the first doctoral qualification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These scholarships in New Zealand will refine your research skills according to the current market trends. These research scholarships will combine classroom lectures, tutorials, lab experimentation, assignments, and reading materials. The University of Otago, New Zealand’s first university, started with few resources and has now extended its sphere from Invercargill to Auckland. This international University has a history of passing out around 4500 post-graduates and more than 1500 doctoral students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With 13 flagship research centers, the University of Otago has gained research and teaching excellence by winning three Prime Minister’s Science Prizes in the last decade. New Zealand’s top university has spent $208 million in external research funding. The Otago has topped the TEC’s Educational performance indicators that express the performance and retention rating of the students. Moreover, the University has won the Supreme Award six times over the past nine years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The international scholarship opportunities by the University of Otago will prove to be a worthy option for the participants. The Otago students are recognized for their negotiating, interpersonal, conceptual, independent judgment, and analytical skills. Therefore, global employers used to love Otago students. More than 90% of Otago students get jobs quickly once they complete their education. You will get the opportunity to learn from world-class lecturers and professors who stand shoulder-to-shoulder with the best globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34;&gt;University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand: &lt;a href=&#34;#university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Zealand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;University of Otago&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;number-of-scholarships&#34;&gt;Number of Scholarships: &lt;a href=&#34;#number-of-scholarships&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;180 University of Otago postgraduate research scholarships in New Zealand&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;degree-level&#34;&gt;Degree Level: &lt;a href=&#34;#degree-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional Doctorates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scholarship-duration&#34;&gt;Scholarship Duration: &lt;a href=&#34;#scholarship-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The duration of the research scholarship is 36 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-university-of-otago-scholarship-benefits-2024&#34;&gt;The University of Otago Scholarship Benefits 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#the-university-of-otago-scholarship-benefits-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support funding for doctoral research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NZ $32,544 stipend annually for Doctors of Philosophy and other professional doctorates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Domestic tuition fee waiver for Doctors of Philosophy for up to 36 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition fee waiver for up to 36 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exposure to conducting research in an International environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awareness of advanced research methods and techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-of-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria of the University of Otago Scholarships 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-of-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All domestic and international students can apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completion of Master’s degree with at least 0.75 EFTS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relevant advanced papers should be followed with the degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case a Master’s degree is not completed, the grades of all relevant advanced-level papers will be considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If prior qualifications are completed by any other University, the GPA score should be mentioned on the transcripts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s potential for research is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s track record of research is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommendation of the concerned Head of the department is necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34;&gt;How to Apply for the University of Otago Scholarships 2024? &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students have to apply through the University’s website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete the application for admission with the relevant qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer all questions carefully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review your application form carefully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After the submission of the application, an invitation to apply for the scholarship will be received in your e-Vision portal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;selection-criteria-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34;&gt;Selection Criteria for the University of Otago Scholarships in New Zealand: &lt;a href=&#34;#selection-criteria-for-the-university-of-otago-scholarships-in-new-zealand&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research potential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic merit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;application-deadline&#34;&gt;Application Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#application-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no closing date. The applicant may apply anytime throughout the year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.otago.ac.nz/study/scholarships/database/search/otago014687.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25 | Study in Australia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25--study-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25--study-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25 | Study in Australia
by Scholarships Corner | Aug 19, 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;University of Sydney scholarship, australian scholarships
The Research Training Program RTP scholarship in Australia valued at up to $143,881, is funded by the Australian Government and is intended to support exceptional international research student by paying tuition fees and providing a stipend for living expenses. The University of Sydney is ranked #1 in sustainability, social impact, and educational impact in addition to being exceptionally prominent in a wide range of academic fields, including business, engineering, geography, technology, arts, architecture, and education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The range of topics covered by university research centre is broad and diverse, ranging from nano science to linguistics. Comprehensive disciplinary knowledge supports the depth of expertise throughout the faculties and schools. The institute has significant capability in more than 20 important research fields. Researchers from all around the world come together as part of multidisciplinary projects to tackle some of the most critical global issues, such as youth mental health, chronic illness incidence rising, and climate change. This international postgraduate scholarship will provide students the opportunity to learn and gain experience  from other fellows researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sydney Indigenous Research Hub provides growth and mentorship for faculty members and students pursuing higher degrees in research, as well as coordination and support for all Indigenous research at the university. You can find research and researchers there, as well as acquire new skills, expand your research networks, find a mentor, and generally experience about research that is relevant to Indigenous people globally. This Research training program scholarship will provide a perfect environment for conducting your all research related activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Areas for the University of Sydeny scholarships include include Agricultural and veterinary sciences, Biological sciences, Built environment and design, Chemical sciences, Commerce, management, tourism and services, Creative arts and writing, Earth sciences, Economics, Education, Engineering, Environmental sciences, History and archaeology, Human society, Informational and computing sciences, Language, communication and culture, Law and legal studies, Mathematical sciences, Medical and health sciences, Philosophy and religious studies, Physical sciences, Psychology and cognitive sciences, and Technology. Choose the field of your interest and start your journey of  research Scholarships in Austrlia  before the deadline approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34;&gt;University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25: &lt;a href=&#34;#university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-organization&#34;&gt;Host organization: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-organization&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australian Government&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scholarship-location&#34;&gt;Scholarship Location: &lt;a href=&#34;#scholarship-location&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The University of Sydney&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;university-of-sydney-scholarship-duration&#34;&gt;University of Sydney Scholarship Duration: &lt;a href=&#34;#university-of-sydney-scholarship-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years for Research Doctorate, 1.75 years for Research Master’s studies..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-university-of-sydney-scholarship-2024&#34;&gt;Benefits of University of Sydney Scholarship 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-university-of-sydney-scholarship-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The RTP stipends will be valued at $40,109 per annum as per 2024 rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The RTP International Scholarship will provide a stipend to help scholars to bear their living costs and health expenses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition fees will be fully funded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visa Application fee will be waived off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no admission or registration fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to explore the beautiful city of Sydney.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria for University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RTP scholarships are very competitive and are awarded based on academic merit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research publications will also be highly considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants can be a new or already enrolled international postgraduate research student.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must have an excellent record of academic achievement and should have research potential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates should have an unconditional admission offer letter or should be currently enrolled in a master’s degree or PhD at the University of Sydney.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-australia-scholarships-in-2024&#34;&gt;How to apply for the Australia Scholarships in 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-australia-scholarships-in-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While applying for postgraduate research degree application, applicants should select the check box for getting considered for RTP Scholarship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A separate application for scholarship is not needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application of research degree course must be submitted before the relevant RTP deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship&#34;&gt;Documents Required for University of Sydney RTP Scholarship: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education transcripts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evidence of publications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of English language proficiency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scanned supporting documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valid passport.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australiascholarship-deadline&#34;&gt;AustraliaScholarship Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#australiascholarship-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The last date to apply is 13th September, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sydney.edu.au/scholarships/e/australian-government-rtp-scholarship-international.html#:~:text=The%20Scholarship%20may%20be%20held,maximum%20tenure%20of%20the%20award&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship 2024-25 in Australia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Applications for Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship in Australia for 2025 are now being accepted. The recipients of these fully funded scholarships must enroll in Higher Degree by Research program at Charles Darwin University between January 6, 2025, and March 31, 2025. The Research Training Program (RTP) offers block grants to higher education providers (HEPs) to support local and international students to pursue research doctorates and research masters degrees, which are also known as higher degrees by research (HDRs). Both degrees have funding available for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the RTP are to provide flexible funding arrangements to support training of  students undertaking HDRs at Australian HEPs. The purpose of this international scholarship for Masters and PhD students is to teach skills which are necessary to develop a career in academic and various other sectors of the labour markets. It also supports collaboration between HEPs and industry and other research stakeholders. The skills learned will be helpful for students which will make them empowered and capable of doing great things in their careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through its fully funded scholarship in Australia for international students, CDU is dedicated to giving students great research opportunity. The university, corporations, government, and community organizations give scholarships to help students with the cost of their education. In addition to covering research expenses not directly covered by Australian competitive grants and other sources, the Research Support Program (RSP) funds HEPs for systemic research costs like libraries, labs, consumables, computing centers, and the salaries of support and technical staff. The sponsorship will help you to focus on your research and study rather than worrying about the research expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In CDU scholarship for international and local students, you can study a wide range of disciplines as part of your research degree which include health, Environment and livelihood, Engineering and Information Technology, Education and Arts, Social and Public Policy, Business and Law, Disaster Management, Humanities, Social Sciences and languages, Tropical Agriculture, Aquaculture and Biosecurity. While submitting your application, you have to choose a research project and a potential research supervisor from Charles Darwin University who will assist you throughout your research project. This is an incredible fully funded research scholarship which has so many benefits that will almost end your financial burden of studying in a foreign university.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34;&gt;Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship 2024-25: &lt;a href=&#34;#charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;funded-by&#34;&gt;Funded by &lt;a href=&#34;#funded-by&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australian Government&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charles Darwin University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scholarship-level&#34;&gt;Scholarship level: &lt;a href=&#34;#scholarship-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masters and Doctorate degrees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;benefits-of-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-in-australia&#34;&gt;Benefits of Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship in Australia: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-in-australia&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Australian Government RTP Stipend Scholarships are given to outstanding research students for pursuing an HDR at an Australian institution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The scholarships are offered to help students cover their general living expenses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full time students will be paid AU$32,192 (2024 rate) per annum tax-free.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Part-time students will be paid AU$16,096 (2024 rate) per annum, taxable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid sick leave can be taken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maternity leave will be given.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation allowance for RTP stipend recipients is up to $2,000 for domestic students and $2,500 for international students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria for Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship 2024-25 in Australia: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must be eligible to enroll in a full-time Higher Degree by Research (HDR) program at Charles Darwin University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must meet the academic entry requirements for a Master’s degree by research or a Doctorate by research at Charles Darwin University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a Doctorate scholarship, applicants must have completed both a bachelor’s and a master’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a Master’s scholarship, applicants must have completed a bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International applicants must provide evidence of meeting the minimum English language proficiency requirements of Charles Darwin University. Please visit the University Entry Requirements page for more details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must not be receiving any other financial support that exceeds 75% of the RTP stipend rate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must demonstrate exceptional research potential suitable for an HDR program..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-scholarships-in-australia&#34;&gt;How to apply for Scholarships in Australia: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-scholarships-in-australia&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer all relevant questions in the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the application option carefully (Candidature only; Candidature &amp;amp; Scholarship; or Scholarship only (for those candidates who are currently enrolled in Charles Darwin University or they have already received an offer letter from the university).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should select “Candidature only” if you are applying for a PhD program by Prior Publication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can save your details and complete the form later too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you will select the option ‘save and continue later’, you will get a link in your email which can be clicked to resume the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure that the application is complete by reviewing the checklist given at the end of the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attach all supporting documents to the application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After submitting the form, the application form will be automatically sent to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:degrees@cdu.edu.au&#34;&gt;degrees@cdu.edu.au&lt;/a&gt; and to you as well on your email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship&#34;&gt;Documents Required for Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A copy of your current passport, birth certificate or your residency visa is required for proof of citizenship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photocopy of official academic transcripts and certificates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;for all previous tertiary study. Evidence of supervision which includes email conversation with your potential supervisor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A research outline of 1500-1700 words on the research project you have proposed. It should include title of the project, general research field, brief description, ethical rules and other relevant concerns related to the research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HDR referee report form filled by two referees to testify your academic record.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copy of current CV.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting documents which include publications or portfolios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;charles-darwin-university-scholarships-deadline&#34;&gt;Charles Darwin University Scholarships Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#charles-darwin-university-scholarships-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last date to apply for domestic applicants is 31 October 2024 and for international applicants is 30 September 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cdu.edu.au/research-and-innovation/higher-degree-research/scholarships/competitive-round-scholarship&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 USA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/mandelawashingtonfellowship2025usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/mandelawashingtonfellowship2025usa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2025, The Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 in USA will bring up to 700 young leaders to the United States for an extensive executive-style program aimed at developing skills and enabling Fellows to take on leadership roles in their communities and industries. Selected fellows will participate in a six-week Leadership Institute at a U.S. college or university where they will share their experiences with U.S citizens and other African Fellows and learn from them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this fully-funded fellowship, Fellows will have the opportunity to explore various industries other than their daily work which will help to expand their expertise and strengthen their skills. Other than this, fellows will be able to meet with U.S. Government Officials and renowned business leaders. This US exchange program will enhance your work with the help of new connections, skills, and ideas. After the event will end, fellows can join the global Alumni Network that will be useful for them to look for creative solutions to most common problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will have a life-changing experience from this leadership program. Through this fellowship for Africans, participants will establish powerful networks with both Africans and Americans. You’ll be able to regain your self-confidence and motivation to give back to your community. Students will be studying Business, Civic Engagement, or Public Management hosted by U.S. colleges or universities which will add to their existing knowledge and teach them new concepts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mandela Washington Fellowship does not discriminate against applicants on the basis of any protected characteristic as defined by U.S. law, including race, ethnicity, colour, national origin, sex, age, religion, geographic location, education, income, socioeconomic status, ability, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, or any other. The Fellowship is dedicated to accessibility, fairness, equity, and inclusion. If you belong to one of the countries mentioned above, feel free to apply for this international fellowship program in U.S before the deadline approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-organization&#34;&gt;Host Organization &lt;a href=&#34;#host-organization&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Young African Leaders Initiative (YALI) Network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;mandela-fellowship-location&#34;&gt;Mandela Fellowship Location: &lt;a href=&#34;#mandela-fellowship-location&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington DC, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fellowship-duration&#34;&gt;Fellowship Duration &lt;a href=&#34;#fellowship-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 weeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34;&gt;Benefits of Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 in the USA: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;J-1 visa support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Round-trip travel from the Fellow’s home city to the United States and necessary domestic U.S. travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Departure from an eligible Fellowship country in Africa to the United States&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Six-week Leadership Institute
Concluding Summit in Washington, D.C.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limited accident and sickness benefit plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Housing and meals during the program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optional four-week Professional Development Experience for up to 100 Fellows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fellows will participate in a six-week Leadership Institute at a U.S. college or university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to interact with other fellows attending the event.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fellows will become a part of Global Alumni Network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be no discrimination on the basis of race, gender, color or any other protected characteristic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants will get a chance to meet U.S officials and business executives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This is a wonderful chance to explore USA without financial burden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria for Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025 in the USA: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025-in-the-usa&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be young African leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are between the ages of 25 and 35 years old till September 10, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not have to be either U.S. citizens or permanent residents of U.S.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be eligible to receive a United States J-1 visa.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must not be employees or family members including spouses, parents, children, or siblings of any employees of the U.S. Government Departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be proficient in reading, writing, and speaking English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be citizens and permanent residents of one of the following countries:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Angola, Benin, Botswana, Burkina Faso, Burundi, Cameroon, Cabo Verde, Central African Republic, Chad, Comoros, Republic of the Congo, Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC), Cote d’Ivoire, Djibouti, Equatorial Guinea, Eritrea, Eswatini, Ethiopia, Gabon, The Gambia, Ghana, Guinea, Guinea-Bissau, Kenya, Lesotho, Liberia, Madagascar, Malawi, Mali, Mauritania, Mauritius, Mozambique, Namibia, Niger, Nigeria, Rwanda, Sao Tome and Principe, Senegal, Seychelles, Sierra Leone, Somalia, South Africa, South Sudan, Sudan, Tanzania, Togo, Uganda, Zambia, or Zimbabwe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do not have to be Alumni or former participant of the Mandela Washington Fellowship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025&#34;&gt;How to apply for Mandela Washington Fellowship 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-mandela-washington-fellowship-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin with new User registration on the link given to apply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agree to the terms and conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create your account by entering your email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A confirmation email will be sent on your email address to create a new account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This link will automatically expire after 60 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create your account by entering a password of your email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide the general information asked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide your CV details in the sections already given.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mention your education and professional experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List your professional skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enter your demographic details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mention any previous U.S experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer short essay questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete the application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click the blue button “Review and Submit”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your application will be submitted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selected candidates will then further have interviews.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-mandela-fellowship-2025&#34;&gt;Documents required for Mandela Fellowship 2025: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-mandela-fellowship-2025&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional trainings and certifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community and Volunteer work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Awards, honors, grants and scholarships received.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associations and affiliations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;English language proficiency test scores.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personal statement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International passport.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2025-mandela-fellowship-deadline&#34;&gt;2025 Mandela Fellowship Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#2025-mandela-fellowship-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The last date to apply is 10th September, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mandelawashingtonfellowship.org/apply/&#34;&gt;Apply Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIST Scholarship in South Korea 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/gist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/gist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://scholarshipscorner.website/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/GIST-Scholarships-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;GIST Korea&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology in South Korea welcomes skilled and talented students, researchers, and technical individuals to pursue their MS, PhD, and MS leading to PhD under the GIST Scholarship 2024. The GIST scholarship for international students in Korea provides them with a bright chance to create a strong research base for further development of science and technology. Moreover, the best scholarship in South Korea’s top universities provides opportunities for students to work and promote collaborative foreign and domestic research programs in the industrial sector as well as in academia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GIST scholars are equipped with world-class knowledge and skills regarding science and technology through research-oriented projects and courses. Furthermore, GIST’s fully-funded scholarship is a project of the university with the South Korean Ministry of Science and Technology. The ministry provides full financial support to the students of GIST in order to promote scientific technologists and encourage them toward more innovations. For this, the university offers students multiple fields of study related to science, technology, and research. The GIST university courses include Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Material Science and Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Earth Science and Environmental Engineering, Life Science, Physics and Photon Science, Chemistry and Biomedical Science, Nanobio Materials and Electronics, Integrated Technology, and Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GIST was established by Korean Government in 1993 and since then the institute has been home to world-class researchers and sciencetists. Moreover, the top-notch lecturers of Korean institutes come from GIST. GIST has proved itself as the first national university in Korea which has adopted an innovative educational system based on a comprehensive and foundational science curriculum. Moreover, GIST is the first Korean university that has made a thesis quality certification mandatory thing. That is why the institute is ranked 1st in the number of citations of professors in South Korea for 14 consecutive years and also the GIST is ranked 4th in QS World University Ranking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GIST Scholarships for MS and PhD students is a milestone towards achieving the goal of the institute i.e. A proud creator of future science and technology. In order to lead in the world, all classes are taught in English, and the thesis is also written in the English language. GIST understands the importance of learning and utilizing an international language for better collaboration and development. The scholars of the GIST international scholarship in South Korea will learn the Korean culture while staying for a maximum of three, seven, or eight years for MS, PhD, or Integrated MS/PhD programs respectively. The following comprehensively explains the financial benefits along with the eligibility criteria and an understandable procedure to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gist-scholarship-in-south-korea-2024&#34;&gt;GIST Scholarship in South Korea 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#gist-scholarship-in-south-korea-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South Korea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology (GIST)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;degree-level&#34;&gt;Degree Level: &lt;a href=&#34;#degree-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrated MS and PhD Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-gist-scholarship-in-south-korea&#34;&gt;Benefits of the GIST Scholarship in South Korea: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-the-gist-scholarship-in-south-korea&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All international students will be getting 100% support in the tuition fee i.e. the tuition fee will be waived.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS students will be given a monthly stipend of 140,000 Won.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD students will be given a monthly stipend of 295,000 Won.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both MS and PhD students will be given a meal allowance of 100,000 Won. (Note: Students have to complete at least 9 credits in the previous semester in order to get student and meal allowance).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An international student allowance of 120,000 Won will be given to both MS and PhD students, however, the student has to maintain a 3 or higher GPA out of 4.5 in the previous semester.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All MS students participating in research projects will get a research assistantship of 5,461,249 won per year while PhD students participating in research projects will get a research assistantship of 12,513,688 won per year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A one-way flight to Korea will be reimbursed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;60% of national health insurance will be covered. Health insurance also includes annual medical checkups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-of-the-gist-scholarship-2024-in-south-korea&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria of the GIST Scholarship 2024 in South Korea: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-of-the-gist-scholarship-2024-in-south-korea&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must or expect to hold a final degree before enrollment at GIST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s bachelor’s degree must be equivalent to a Korean bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be an international student.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be proficient in the English language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-gist-scholarship-2024&#34;&gt;How to apply for the GIST Scholarship 2024? &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-gist-scholarship-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to apply online for the GIST South Korea scholarship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to submit a matriculation fee, however, the matriculation fee can be waived on the recommendation of the dean/head of the department/college.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In order to apply successfully, all the applicants must carefully fill out the GIST online application form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t leave blanks instead write NA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-the-gist-scholarships-2023&#34;&gt;Documents Required for the GIST Scholarships 2023: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-the-gist-scholarships-2023&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official degrees and transcripts are required. Apostille is preferred or even notarized copies are acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two letters of recommendation must have the signatures and stamps of the recommenders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The recommenders do not have to send the letters independently or separately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official English language test report i.e. TOEFL (BT) 80 / TOEFL (PBT) 550 / IELTS 6.5 / TOEIC 750 / NEW TEPS 327 is the requirement. In case you do not get your test result in time. Your home university can give you a professional English language proficiency certificate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A copy of the applicant’s passport is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gist-scholarship-application-deadline&#34;&gt;GIST Scholarship Application Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#gist-scholarship-application-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application deadline for the Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology scholarship in South Korea 2024 is October 14, 2023.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gist.ac.kr/iadm/html/sub05/0502.html?mode=V&amp;amp;no=205383&amp;amp;GotoPage=1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
