<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PhD on Tenkr Scholarship</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/tags/phd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PhD on Tenkr Scholarship</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/tags/phd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25 | Study in Australia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25--study-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25--study-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25 | Study in Australia
by Scholarships Corner | Aug 19, 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;University of Sydney scholarship, australian scholarships
The Research Training Program RTP scholarship in Australia valued at up to $143,881, is funded by the Australian Government and is intended to support exceptional international research student by paying tuition fees and providing a stipend for living expenses. The University of Sydney is ranked #1 in sustainability, social impact, and educational impact in addition to being exceptionally prominent in a wide range of academic fields, including business, engineering, geography, technology, arts, architecture, and education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The range of topics covered by university research centre is broad and diverse, ranging from nano science to linguistics. Comprehensive disciplinary knowledge supports the depth of expertise throughout the faculties and schools. The institute has significant capability in more than 20 important research fields. Researchers from all around the world come together as part of multidisciplinary projects to tackle some of the most critical global issues, such as youth mental health, chronic illness incidence rising, and climate change. This international postgraduate scholarship will provide students the opportunity to learn and gain experience  from other fellows researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sydney Indigenous Research Hub provides growth and mentorship for faculty members and students pursuing higher degrees in research, as well as coordination and support for all Indigenous research at the university. You can find research and researchers there, as well as acquire new skills, expand your research networks, find a mentor, and generally experience about research that is relevant to Indigenous people globally. This Research training program scholarship will provide a perfect environment for conducting your all research related activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Areas for the University of Sydeny scholarships include include Agricultural and veterinary sciences, Biological sciences, Built environment and design, Chemical sciences, Commerce, management, tourism and services, Creative arts and writing, Earth sciences, Economics, Education, Engineering, Environmental sciences, History and archaeology, Human society, Informational and computing sciences, Language, communication and culture, Law and legal studies, Mathematical sciences, Medical and health sciences, Philosophy and religious studies, Physical sciences, Psychology and cognitive sciences, and Technology. Choose the field of your interest and start your journey of  research Scholarships in Austrlia  before the deadline approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34;&gt;University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25: &lt;a href=&#34;#university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-organization&#34;&gt;Host organization: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-organization&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australian Government&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scholarship-location&#34;&gt;Scholarship Location: &lt;a href=&#34;#scholarship-location&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The University of Sydney&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;university-of-sydney-scholarship-duration&#34;&gt;University of Sydney Scholarship Duration: &lt;a href=&#34;#university-of-sydney-scholarship-duration&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 years for Research Doctorate, 1.75 years for Research Master’s studies..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-university-of-sydney-scholarship-2024&#34;&gt;Benefits of University of Sydney Scholarship 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-university-of-sydney-scholarship-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The RTP stipends will be valued at $40,109 per annum as per 2024 rate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The RTP International Scholarship will provide a stipend to help scholars to bear their living costs and health expenses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tuition fees will be fully funded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visa Application fee will be waived off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no admission or registration fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to explore the beautiful city of Sydney.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria for University of Sydney RTP Scholarship 2024-25: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RTP scholarships are very competitive and are awarded based on academic merit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research publications will also be highly considered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants can be a new or already enrolled international postgraduate research student.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must have an excellent record of academic achievement and should have research potential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates should have an unconditional admission offer letter or should be currently enrolled in a master’s degree or PhD at the University of Sydney.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-australia-scholarships-in-2024&#34;&gt;How to apply for the Australia Scholarships in 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-australia-scholarships-in-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While applying for postgraduate research degree application, applicants should select the check box for getting considered for RTP Scholarship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A separate application for scholarship is not needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application of research degree course must be submitted before the relevant RTP deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship&#34;&gt;Documents Required for University of Sydney RTP Scholarship: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-university-of-sydney-rtp-scholarship&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education transcripts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evidence of publications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proof of English language proficiency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scanned supporting documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valid passport.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;australiascholarship-deadline&#34;&gt;AustraliaScholarship Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#australiascholarship-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The last date to apply is 13th September, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sydney.edu.au/scholarships/e/australian-government-rtp-scholarship-international.html#:~:text=The%20Scholarship%20may%20be%20held,maximum%20tenure%20of%20the%20award&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship 2024-25 in Australia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:59:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Applications for Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship in Australia for 2025 are now being accepted. The recipients of these fully funded scholarships must enroll in Higher Degree by Research program at Charles Darwin University between January 6, 2025, and March 31, 2025. The Research Training Program (RTP) offers block grants to higher education providers (HEPs) to support local and international students to pursue research doctorates and research masters degrees, which are also known as higher degrees by research (HDRs). Both degrees have funding available for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The objectives of the RTP are to provide flexible funding arrangements to support training of  students undertaking HDRs at Australian HEPs. The purpose of this international scholarship for Masters and PhD students is to teach skills which are necessary to develop a career in academic and various other sectors of the labour markets. It also supports collaboration between HEPs and industry and other research stakeholders. The skills learned will be helpful for students which will make them empowered and capable of doing great things in their careers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through its fully funded scholarship in Australia for international students, CDU is dedicated to giving students great research opportunity. The university, corporations, government, and community organizations give scholarships to help students with the cost of their education. In addition to covering research expenses not directly covered by Australian competitive grants and other sources, the Research Support Program (RSP) funds HEPs for systemic research costs like libraries, labs, consumables, computing centers, and the salaries of support and technical staff. The sponsorship will help you to focus on your research and study rather than worrying about the research expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In CDU scholarship for international and local students, you can study a wide range of disciplines as part of your research degree which include health, Environment and livelihood, Engineering and Information Technology, Education and Arts, Social and Public Policy, Business and Law, Disaster Management, Humanities, Social Sciences and languages, Tropical Agriculture, Aquaculture and Biosecurity. While submitting your application, you have to choose a research project and a potential research supervisor from Charles Darwin University who will assist you throughout your research project. This is an incredible fully funded research scholarship which has so many benefits that will almost end your financial burden of studying in a foreign university.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34;&gt;Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship 2024-25: &lt;a href=&#34;#charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;funded-by&#34;&gt;Funded by &lt;a href=&#34;#funded-by&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Australian Government&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charles Darwin University&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scholarship-level&#34;&gt;Scholarship level: &lt;a href=&#34;#scholarship-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masters and Doctorate degrees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;benefits-of-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-in-australia&#34;&gt;Benefits of Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship in Australia: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-in-australia&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Australian Government RTP Stipend Scholarships are given to outstanding research students for pursuing an HDR at an Australian institution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The scholarships are offered to help students cover their general living expenses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full time students will be paid AU$32,192 (2024 rate) per annum tax-free.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Part-time students will be paid AU$16,096 (2024 rate) per annum, taxable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid sick leave can be taken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maternity leave will be given.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Relocation allowance for RTP stipend recipients is up to $2,000 for domestic students and $2,500 for international students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria for Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship 2024-25 in Australia: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship-2024-25-in-australia&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must be eligible to enroll in a full-time Higher Degree by Research (HDR) program at Charles Darwin University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must meet the academic entry requirements for a Master’s degree by research or a Doctorate by research at Charles Darwin University.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a Doctorate scholarship, applicants must have completed both a bachelor’s and a master’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For a Master’s scholarship, applicants must have completed a bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;International applicants must provide evidence of meeting the minimum English language proficiency requirements of Charles Darwin University. Please visit the University Entry Requirements page for more details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must not be receiving any other financial support that exceeds 75% of the RTP stipend rate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applicants must demonstrate exceptional research potential suitable for an HDR program..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-scholarships-in-australia&#34;&gt;How to apply for Scholarships in Australia: &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-scholarships-in-australia&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer all relevant questions in the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the application option carefully (Candidature only; Candidature &amp;amp; Scholarship; or Scholarship only (for those candidates who are currently enrolled in Charles Darwin University or they have already received an offer letter from the university).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You should select “Candidature only” if you are applying for a PhD program by Prior Publication.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can save your details and complete the form later too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you will select the option ‘save and continue later’, you will get a link in your email which can be clicked to resume the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make sure that the application is complete by reviewing the checklist given at the end of the form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attach all supporting documents to the application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After submitting the form, the application form will be automatically sent to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:degrees@cdu.edu.au&#34;&gt;degrees@cdu.edu.au&lt;/a&gt; and to you as well on your email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship&#34;&gt;Documents Required for Charles Darwin University RTP Scholarship: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-charles-darwin-university-rtp-scholarship&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A copy of your current passport, birth certificate or your residency visa is required for proof of citizenship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Photocopy of official academic transcripts and certificates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;for all previous tertiary study. Evidence of supervision which includes email conversation with your potential supervisor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A research outline of 1500-1700 words on the research project you have proposed. It should include title of the project, general research field, brief description, ethical rules and other relevant concerns related to the research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;HDR referee report form filled by two referees to testify your academic record.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copy of current CV.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supporting documents which include publications or portfolios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;charles-darwin-university-scholarships-deadline&#34;&gt;Charles Darwin University Scholarships Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#charles-darwin-university-scholarships-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last date to apply for domestic applicants is 31 October 2024 and for international applicants is 30 September 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cdu.edu.au/research-and-innovation/higher-degree-research/scholarships/competitive-round-scholarship&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIST Scholarship in South Korea 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/gist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tenkr-scholarship/posts/gist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://scholarshipscorner.website/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/GIST-Scholarships-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;GIST Korea&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology in South Korea welcomes skilled and talented students, researchers, and technical individuals to pursue their MS, PhD, and MS leading to PhD under the GIST Scholarship 2024. The GIST scholarship for international students in Korea provides them with a bright chance to create a strong research base for further development of science and technology. Moreover, the best scholarship in South Korea’s top universities provides opportunities for students to work and promote collaborative foreign and domestic research programs in the industrial sector as well as in academia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GIST scholars are equipped with world-class knowledge and skills regarding science and technology through research-oriented projects and courses. Furthermore, GIST’s fully-funded scholarship is a project of the university with the South Korean Ministry of Science and Technology. The ministry provides full financial support to the students of GIST in order to promote scientific technologists and encourage them toward more innovations. For this, the university offers students multiple fields of study related to science, technology, and research. The GIST university courses include Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Material Science and Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Earth Science and Environmental Engineering, Life Science, Physics and Photon Science, Chemistry and Biomedical Science, Nanobio Materials and Electronics, Integrated Technology, and Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GIST was established by Korean Government in 1993 and since then the institute has been home to world-class researchers and sciencetists. Moreover, the top-notch lecturers of Korean institutes come from GIST. GIST has proved itself as the first national university in Korea which has adopted an innovative educational system based on a comprehensive and foundational science curriculum. Moreover, GIST is the first Korean university that has made a thesis quality certification mandatory thing. That is why the institute is ranked 1st in the number of citations of professors in South Korea for 14 consecutive years and also the GIST is ranked 4th in QS World University Ranking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GIST Scholarships for MS and PhD students is a milestone towards achieving the goal of the institute i.e. A proud creator of future science and technology. In order to lead in the world, all classes are taught in English, and the thesis is also written in the English language. GIST understands the importance of learning and utilizing an international language for better collaboration and development. The scholars of the GIST international scholarship in South Korea will learn the Korean culture while staying for a maximum of three, seven, or eight years for MS, PhD, or Integrated MS/PhD programs respectively. The following comprehensively explains the financial benefits along with the eligibility criteria and an understandable procedure to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gist-scholarship-in-south-korea-2024&#34;&gt;GIST Scholarship in South Korea 2024: &lt;a href=&#34;#gist-scholarship-in-south-korea-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-country&#34;&gt;Host Country: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-country&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;South Korea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;host-university&#34;&gt;Host University: &lt;a href=&#34;#host-university&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology (GIST)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;degree-level&#34;&gt;Degree Level: &lt;a href=&#34;#degree-level&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Master’s degree program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD degree program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrated MS and PhD Program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;benefits-of-the-gist-scholarship-in-south-korea&#34;&gt;Benefits of the GIST Scholarship in South Korea: &lt;a href=&#34;#benefits-of-the-gist-scholarship-in-south-korea&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All international students will be getting 100% support in the tuition fee i.e. the tuition fee will be waived.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MS students will be given a monthly stipend of 140,000 Won.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhD students will be given a monthly stipend of 295,000 Won.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Both MS and PhD students will be given a meal allowance of 100,000 Won. (Note: Students have to complete at least 9 credits in the previous semester in order to get student and meal allowance).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An international student allowance of 120,000 Won will be given to both MS and PhD students, however, the student has to maintain a 3 or higher GPA out of 4.5 in the previous semester.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All MS students participating in research projects will get a research assistantship of 5,461,249 won per year while PhD students participating in research projects will get a research assistantship of 12,513,688 won per year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A one-way flight to Korea will be reimbursed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;60% of national health insurance will be covered. Health insurance also includes annual medical checkups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;eligibility-criteria-of-the-gist-scholarship-2024-in-south-korea&#34;&gt;Eligibility Criteria of the GIST Scholarship 2024 in South Korea: &lt;a href=&#34;#eligibility-criteria-of-the-gist-scholarship-2024-in-south-korea&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must or expect to hold a final degree before enrollment at GIST.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant’s bachelor’s degree must be equivalent to a Korean bachelor’s degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be an international student.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant must be proficient in the English language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-apply-for-the-gist-scholarship-2024&#34;&gt;How to apply for the GIST Scholarship 2024? &lt;a href=&#34;#how-to-apply-for-the-gist-scholarship-2024&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to apply online for the GIST South Korea scholarship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The applicant has to submit a matriculation fee, however, the matriculation fee can be waived on the recommendation of the dean/head of the department/college.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In order to apply successfully, all the applicants must carefully fill out the GIST online application form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t leave blanks instead write NA.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;documents-required-for-the-gist-scholarships-2023&#34;&gt;Documents Required for the GIST Scholarships 2023: &lt;a href=&#34;#documents-required-for-the-gist-scholarships-2023&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official degrees and transcripts are required. Apostille is preferred or even notarized copies are acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two letters of recommendation must have the signatures and stamps of the recommenders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The recommenders do not have to send the letters independently or separately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official English language test report i.e. TOEFL (BT) 80 / TOEFL (PBT) 550 / IELTS 6.5 / TOEIC 750 / NEW TEPS 327 is the requirement. In case you do not get your test result in time. Your home university can give you a professional English language proficiency certificate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A copy of the applicant’s passport is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gist-scholarship-application-deadline&#34;&gt;GIST Scholarship Application Deadline: &lt;a href=&#34;#gist-scholarship-application-deadline&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;🔗&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The application deadline for the Gwangju Institute of Science and Technology scholarship in South Korea 2024 is October 14, 2023.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gist.ac.kr/iadm/html/sub05/0502.html?mode=V&amp;amp;no=205383&amp;amp;GotoPage=1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Official link&lt;/a&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
